http://www.audiologyonline.com/general/privacy-policy

Copyright © 2020 AudiologyOnline - All Rights Reserved
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to www.AudiologyOnline (the “Site”). Except as specifically provided herein, this Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice. Please read it each time you visit the Site. If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy, you may not access and use the Site. Your use of the Site signifies your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.If we make a material change to our privacy practices that involves the use of your Personally Identifiable Information (defined below), we will inform you through a posting on our homepage, by email when available, and through an update to this Privacy Policy. We will inform you of any non-material changes to our privacy practices, or changes that do not involve your Personally Identifiable Information, by posting an updated Privacy Policy only. Your continued use of the AudiologyOnline Site after we make changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of those changes.IntroductionInformation We Collect About YouInformation Collected by Third Parties Not Acting on AudiologyOnline's BehalfChildren Under the Age of 13How We Use Your InformationDisclosure of Your InformationHow AudiologyOnline Handles Privacy and Security InternallyManaging Your InformationEntire Agreement, Additional Terms, Waiver, and SeverabilityYour California Privacy RightsContact UsIntroductionAudiologyOnline is a website owned and operated by continued.com, LLC (“continued”, “AudiologyOnline”, “we”, “our” or “us”).Use of the Site is governed by the laws of the United States. When you provide us with information, you acknowledge that the information will be stored and processed on servers located in the United States. No one under the age of 13 may use the Site. If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please have your parents review this Privacy Policy with you.The Site links to other sites. Once you enter another website (whether through an advertisement, service, or content link), be aware that AudiologyOnline is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to look for and review the privacy statements of each and every website you visit through a link or advertisement on AudiologyOnline.While you may use much of AudiologyOnline without registration, some of the specific tools and services on our Site require registration. If you use our Site without registering, the only information we collect will be non-Personally Identifiable Information through the use of features like cookies and web beacons as described in “Non-Personally Identifiable Information We Collect About You” below. If you choose to register with our Site for educational courses or other services, we require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information, as described in “Identifiable Information We Collect About You” below. “Personally Identifiable Information” means information that identifies a person, such as the person’s full name, home address, email address, telephone number, credit card information or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact you.You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the Personally Identifiable Information you submit to AudiologyOnline. Inaccurate information will affect the information you receive when using our Site and tools and our ability to contact you as outlined in this Privacy Policy. For example, your email address should be kept current because that it is how we communicate with you.Information We Collect About YouNon-Personally Identifiable InformationEven if you do not register with AudiologyOnline, we collect non-Personally Identifiable Information about your use of our Site, special promotions and newsletters.CookiesWe collect non-Personally Identifiable Information about your use of our Site and your use of the websites of selected corporate partners (“Corporate Partners”) and advertisers through the use of cookies.A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Every computer is assigned a different cookie by AudiologyOnline. The information collected by cookies (i) helps us dynamically generate advertising and content on web pages or in newsletters, (ii) allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our Site and selected corporate partners' and advertisers' sites, (iii) how many people open our emails, and (iv) for what purposes these actions are being taken. We may use cookie information to target certain advertisements to your browser or to determine the popularity of certain content or advertisements. Cookies are also used to facilitate a user's log-in, as navigation aides and as session timers.Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. If you reject our cookies, certain functions and conveniences of our Site may not work properly but you do not have to accept our cookies in order to productively use our Site. We do not link non-Personally Identifiable Information from cookies to Personally Identifiable Information without your permission.Tracking Pixels/Web BeaconsSome pages of the Site may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages and for other related Site statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain Site content and verifying system and server integrity).Personally Identifiable InformationWe collect Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to us when you register as a member of AudiologyOnline and/or when you update your member profile. We use the Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to respond to your questions, provide you the specific services you select, send you emails about Site maintenance and updates, and inform you of significant changes to this Privacy Policy as described herein.Newsletters and Emails to YouAt registration and at various times as you use AudiologyOnline, you will be given the option of receiving recurring informational/promotional newsletters via email from AudiologyOnline and/or directly from third parties. At the time you sign up for our email newsletters or any time thereafter, you can choose to opt-out of receiving additional promotional emails from AudiologyOnline.In order to subscribe to such newsletters via email, we need your contact information, such as name and email address. You can unsubscribe from the newsletters by simply clicking on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any email newsletter. You will be taken to a webpage where you can choose to update your subscription settings or unsubscribe from all AudiologyOnline newsletters. You may also unsubscribe or change any of your email preferences by clicking on the applicable links in your email newsletter or by changing your profile within AudiologyOnline. If you are experiencing difficulties with our automated unsubscribe service, you can email AudiologyOnline Customer Service at webmaster@AudiologyOnline. AudiologyOnline Customer Service will unsubscribe you from that newsletter in two to three business days.As a part of your membership on AudiologyOnline you may receive certain emails related to your account and CEU activity. These emails allow AudiologyOnline to communicate important information to our users.In some cases, when you click on a link or an advertisement in an email or newsletter, your browser may be momentarily directed to the website of a third party which, acting on behalf of AudiologyOnline, notes or “counts” your response to the email or newsletter before re-directing your browser to its proper destination; this re-direction process will not be apparent to you.When you use AudiologyOnline’s “Email a Friend” function or “Refer a Friend” function, AudiologyOnline emails the article, invitation or other content you designate to your friend's email address and lists your email address as the sender. AudiologyOnline uses the friend's email address only for the purpose of sending your friend the email you requested. While we store both email addresses, we do not use them for any other purpose unless disclosed to you at the time you send the email.Emails You Send to AudiologyOnlineThis Privacy Policy does not protect you when you send content, business information, ideas, concepts or inventions to AudiologyOnline by email. If you want to keep content or business information, ideas, concepts or inventions private or proprietary, do not send them in an email to AudiologyOnline. We try to answer every email within 48 business hours, but are not always able to do so.Discussion Boards and other Public/Classroom ForumsAs a service to our users, AudiologyOnline features discussion boards and other public/classroom forums where users with similar interests or medical conditions can share information and support one another or where users can post questions for experts to answer. We also offer online discussions moderated by medical or healthcare experts.Any information shared (including Personally Identifiable Information and your personal health information (“Personal Health Information”) that you reveal in a discussion forum, message board, “Ask The Expert” posting, or online classroom discussion is by design open to the public and is not a private, secure service. You should think carefully before disclosing any Personally Identifiable Information, health, or similar information in any public forum. This includes online course evaluations and comments. What you have written may be seen, disclosed to or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict, including to contact you for unauthorized purposes.Profile Information – Professional NetworkWe collect user information when you fill out a profile. A complete profile includes professional information such as: job title, education, qualification, skills, license information, etc. This helps site members, corporate partners, recruiters, and other professional entities connect with one another.After you create a profile or apply for a job, you may choose to provide additional information in your profile, such as descriptions of your skills, professional experience, and educational background. You can list honors, awards, professional affiliations, group memberships, and other information including hobbies and interests. Providing additional information enables you to derive more benefit from our Career Services by helping you express your professional identity; find other professionals, opportunities, and information; and help recruiters and business opportunities find you.You can choose what personal information you provide in addition to the information required for registration (name, email, education and work experience). Most of your profile, as well as all content that you post within the profile, is publicly displayed, so please do not provide personal information you do not want to be public. We may use and share information you provide in a profile in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. You may change your privacy settings at any time to not display certain information such as contact information or displaying your profile to the public. You may turn off your profile at any time so that it is not displayed publicly by selecting the proper account settings. By applying for a job or actively seeking a job within the website, you are making your profile information visible to recruiters and other professionals. This information may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict, including to contact you for unauthorized purposes.User Communications – CareerMailWith certain communications you send within our site, the recipient can see your name, email address, and/or profile information depending on your privacy settings.Many communications that you initiate through our site will list your name and primary email address in the header of the message. Messages you initiate may also provide the recipient with aggregate information about your network (for example, how many people are in your professional network). Other communications that you initiate through the site, like a request for an introduction, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal email address contact information. Once you have connected with an individual, regardless of who sent the invitation, your profile information will be shared with that individual.Talent Recruiting, Professional Opportunities, and MarketingWe offer a career partner service to recruiters and other professionals, which can be used to search for, organize, and communicate with potential job candidates or offer business opportunities. In some cases we allow the export of public profile information.We offer customized people-search functionality along with organizational and communications tools (including activity alerts) as part of our talent recruiting, marketing and professional opportunities. These services allow subscribers to access limited information from members’ public profiles, such as name, headline, current company, current title, and location, in order to effectively manage candidate sourcing. You may limit or prevent such subscribers from accessing your profile information by configuring your public profile visibility settings to restrict access to these fields. We do not provide email or other contact information to these subscribers. However, if you post that information as part of your profile it will be available to them and others. A recruiter or other such subscriber may also manage and store information it has independently obtained about you outside of our services, such as a resume, in connection with our platform. Any personal information obtained independently of our site will not be added by us to your profile and is not under our control but is subject to the policies of our recruiting, marketing or professional subscriber. We store such information on behalf of such subscriber who can remove it at any time. We do not further process such information.Market ResearchFrom time to time the AudiologyOnline market research department, or its operations contractors acting on its behalf, conducts online research surveys in order to gather feedback about our Site, our Corporate Partners and opinions on important healthcare issues, through email invitations, pop-up surveys and online focus groups.When participating in a survey, we may ask you to submit Personally Identifiable Information. This Personally Identifiable Information is used for research purposes, and is not used for sales solicitations. When a survey is sponsored by a third party, aggregate information of the survey results is reported to the sponsor in a way that does not specifically and individually identify your Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information collected through market research will only be used by AudiologyOnline and its operations contractors and will not be given or sold to a third party without your consent.In addition to collecting survey responses from our members, cookies may be used to authenticate respondents or to help you pick up where you left off in a survey. If you have cookies disabled you may not be able to participate in some studies. Cookies may be used to connect survey data with AudiologyOnline site usage characteristics. You will be notified when we would like to use cookies in this way and your consent will be requested for these cookies.Information Collected by Third Parties Not Acting on AudiologyOnline's BehalfCorporate Partners or advertisers on AudiologyOnline may use their own cookies in the banner advertisements served on AudiologyOnline and in emails, special promotions or newsletters we send you. Some advertisers use companies other than AudiologyOnline to serve their ads and to monitor users' responses to ads, and these companies (“Ad Servers”) may also collect non-Personally Identifiable Information through the use of cookies on our Site. In certain situations, information collection may be facilitated by momentarily directing your browser to the website of an Ad Server or other third party acting on behalf of the Corporate Partner, or advertiser before re-directing your browser to its proper destination (e.g., back to AudiologyOnline to show the ad, or to the advertiser's website); this re-direction process will not be apparent to you.We do not control these third parties' use of cookies, or how they manage the non-Personally Identifiable Information they gather through them. However, we do require Corporate Partners, advertisers and Ad Servers who collect cookie information through our Site to agree that they will not collect any Personally Identifiable Information from our Site without your consent. They have promised us they will not link any non-Personally Identifiable Information collected by them through cookies in advertising banners on our Site to Personally Identifiable Information they or others collect. Certain Ad Servers allow you to prevent them from collecting data through the use of cookies. In order to do so, you must opt-out of such data collection with each individual site. Currently, you can opt-out of cookies for several Ad Servers by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative gateway opt-out site. This website will also allow you to review the Ad Server's privacy policies.Children Under the Age of 13Our Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this application or on or through any of its features, register on the Site, make any purchases through the Site, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Site, if any, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at the email address listed at the end of this Privacy Policy.How We Use Your InformationWe may use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:To present our Site and its contents to you.To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it including CE reporting.To provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal notices.To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.To notify you about changes to our Site or any products or services we offer or provide through it.To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Site.To process and deliver contest entries and rewards.In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.For any other purpose with your consent.We may also use your information to contact you about our own goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, you may opt out by contacting us at the appropriate email address listed at the end of this policy, or through other methods identified in this policy. We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.Disclosure of Your InformationWe may disclosure your Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information as described below.Personally Identifiable InformationWe may disclose Personally Identifiable Information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:To our subsidiaries and affiliates.To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep the information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.To an Employer or Organization who has purchased a group of memberships. This can include but is not limited to course selection, exam scores, course evaluation comments and CEU transcripts.To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our Site users is among the assets transferred.To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.With your consent.To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request. In the event that we are legally compelled to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to a third party, we will attempt to notify you unless doing so would violate the law or court order.To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.We may also release Personally Identifiable Information to third parties:To comply with reporting requirements set forth by associations whose continuing education credits are offered.In certain cases where membership is purchased by a third party, to comply with reporting requirements of the third party.In special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others.To comply with arrangements made with our corporate partners as it relates to both live and pre-recorded continuing education courses.Additionally, we may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third-party organizations for continuing education courses. For your convenience there are links to continuing education courses hosted by AudiologyOnline, but managed and operated by companies and organizations other than AudiologyOnline (“Third Party Corporate Partner Companies and Organizations”).These Third Party Companies and Organizations provide content or services, including continuing education courses through our Site. These continuing education course links may be found in advertisements, referenced within content, or placed beside the names or logos of Corporate Partners. AudiologyOnline will disclose limited Personally Identifiable Information to these Third Party Corporate Partner Companies and Organizations as it relates to continuing education courses provided by a specific Third Party Corporate Partner. (Example - if a person registers for a particular continuing education course provided by Corporate Partner "A" then AudiologyOnline will provide Corporate Partner “A” with limited Personally Identifiable Information as it relates to the course and the course participant).AudiologyOnline does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices of these organizations. If you choose to participate in a continuing education course using one of these Third Party Company or Organization continuing education courses, you should review the privacy policy posted by this other company or organization to understand how that Third Party Organization collects and uses your Personally Identifiable Information.Non-Personally Identifiable InformationAudiologyOnline may provide aggregate or non-personally identifiable information to third parties without limitation. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of users of our Site and the activities they conduct while on our Site. We might also inform a company (that may or may not be an advertiser on our Site) that “30% of our users live east of the Mississippi” or that “25% of our users are in private practice.” Depending on the circumstances, we may or may not charge third parties for this aggregate information. We require parties with whom we share aggregate information to agree that they will not attempt to make this information personally identifiable, such as by combining it with other databases.How AudiologyOnline Handles Privacy and Security InternallyWe take reasonable measures to protect your Personally Identifiable Information. Listed below are some of the security procedures that AudiologyOnline uses to protect your privacy:Requires both a personal username and a password in order for users to access their Personally Identifiable Information.Uses firewalls to protect information held in our servers.Utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL/TLS) encryption in transmitting Personally Identifiable Information to our servers. In order to take advantage of encryption technology, you must have an Internet browser which supports 128-bit encryption.Closely monitors the limited number of AudiologyOnline employees who have potential access to your Personally Identifiable Information.Requires all AudiologyOnline employees to abide by our Privacy Policy and be subject to disciplinary action if they violate it.Backs up our systems to protect the integrity of your Personally Identifiable Information.Despite AudiologyOnline's efforts to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, there is always some risk that an unauthorized third party may find a way around our security systems or that transmissions of your information over the Internet will be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site and are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk.The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Site like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Site.Managing Your InformationAudiologyOnline contains tools that collect and store self-reported data. These tools allow you to correct, update or review information you have submitted by going back to the specific tool, logging-in and making the desired changes.You may delete your Personally Identifiable Information from our systems by instructing us to do so via email to webmaster@AudiologyOnline. Within a reasonable time after your request, we will delete your Personally Identifiable Information from our active databases and where feasible from our back-up media. You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to AudiologyOnline from our servers.We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.If you delete your submissions and other public information from the Site, copies of that information may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Site users.Entire Agreement, Additional Terms, Waiver, and SeverabilityThe Terms and Conditions for AudiologyOnline are hereby incorporated by reference and made a part hereof. The Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy constitute the entire agreement between you and us with respect to use of this Site. Additional terms and conditions may apply when you enter contests, purchase products or services, use third party services or access linked websites. Should any provision of this Privacy Policy be held invalid, unlawful or for any reason unenforceable, then the invalid, unlawful or unenforceable provision shall be severable from the remaining provisions. Such invalid, unlawful or unenforceable provision shall not affect the validity or enforceability of the remaining provisions.Your California Privacy RightsWe comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act of 2003, California Business and Professional Code 22575 - 22579. If you are a California resident, we will, upon your written request, provide you with: (a) the names and addresses of all third parties to which we have disclosed your Personally Identifiable Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes (if any); (b) the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year; and (c) if the nature of the third party direct marketer’s business cannot be reasonably determined by the third party’s name, examples of the products or services marketed. In order to obtain this information, please contact us using either of the methods described below. We do not respond to Do Not Track browser signals.Contact UsPlease direct any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy to webmaster@AudiologyOnline. You may also write to AudiologyOnline’s Privacy Help Desk at:AudiologyOnline12333 Sowden RdSte. B. #79931Houston, TX 77080-2059
